麦克斯  你猜阿憨在吧台边干嘛
Max, guess what Han's doing at the counter?
至少不会是从上俯视吧台面
Well, I know it's not towering over it.
他在为餐厅制作特色酒
He's creating signature drinks for the diner.
我的建议是  任何家常毒物淋刨冰上即可
I suggested any household poison over shaved ice.
阿憨  这主意太蠢了
Han, this is a stupid idea.
是厄尔的主意
It was Earl's.
那就太天才了
Then it's genius.
是啊  我喝了一下午免费酒了
Yep, I've been drinking all afternoon for free.
我用的全是上层的好酒
Now, I've used only top shelf liquor.
提问  谁帮你从上层拿下来的
Question: Who got it down for you?
第一杯  "麦克斯"  只有威士忌
First up: "The Max". It's just whiskey.
加冰块  就跟麦克斯的工作一样
On the rocks, like Max's job.
无论如何  我的杯口要有盐巴[屁眼咸]
Whatever mine is, I want my rim salted.
你当然是啦
Of course you do.
"厄尔"则是啥都有的古典鸡尾酒
Earl's is an Old Fashioned with everything.
再给我倒杯我自己
Pour me another me.
很不想说出来  但我很随便[很顺口]
I hate to say it, but I go down easy.
"卡洛琳"是放在微冰杯里的柠檬杜松子酒
"The Caroline" is Lemon Schnapps in a slightly frosty glass.
因为我这人如同冰雪女王般冰凉酷炫吗
Because of my cool, Grace Kelly kind of demeanor?
不  是因为酒品店的柠檬杜松子酒刚好打折
No, because they had a sale on Lemon Schnapps at Beverage Barn.
那里不检查年龄就让人买酒吗
Oh, they don't card there?
好了  那"阿憨"是什么酒
Okay, so what's "The Han"?
没激情海滩鸡尾酒吗
A No Sex on the Beach?
我的是经典的摇和法[发抖]马丁尼
Mine is a classic martini, shaken.
就像第一个见过你裸体的女人一样吗
Oh, like the first woman who saw you naked.
修正
Correction.
未来某天见到
Will see you naked.
麦克斯  你猜在你说去一下厕所回来
Max, guess what happened when you were running
结果一去两小时的这中间  发生了什么
to the bathroom real quick, for two hours.
你在小蛋糕橱窗工作
You worked the cupcake window
我去看了自由女神像
while I went to see The Statue of Liberty.
她的头部刚被重新装修
Her head was being renovated.
这城市里大家都在改头换面啊
Everybody in this town is getting work done.
我把咱们最后一件T恤卖掉了
I sold our last cupcake tee!
我们已经比最近20年的
We've sold out more than Robert De Niro
劳勃·狄尼洛还卖座了
in the last 20 years of his career.
岳父大人  靠边闪吧
Well, analyze this, Focker.
我上周就发现我们快没货了
I noticed we were running low last week,
所以我多叫了货
so I ordered more.
我怎么没早点发现呢
How did I not notice those sooner?
大概是因为上次我往里看的时候
Oh, probably because the last time I looked in there,
里面有只老鼠在搞只蟑螂
there was a rat having sex with a cockroach.
它们还在约会呢
You know, they're still dating.
真的吗  我还以为那只是一次约炮
Really? I thought it was a one time thing.
可能试过老鼠屌  再也忘不了吧
Well, I guess once you go rat, you never go back.
谢谢你帮忙订货  我最近一直忙于
Thanks for ordering these, I've just been so busy
准备苏菲的婚前派对
with Sophie's wedding shower.
你干嘛花这么大工夫啊
Yeah, why are you working so hard?
又不是什么大事
It's not a big deal.
我也给我妈办过一次派对
I threw my mother a shower once.
不对  我是把她扔进淋浴[派对]房里
No wait, I threw her in a shower once.
麦克斯  你真的得开始正视这件事
Max, you really need to start making more of a fuss.
这是为苏菲做的  她很在乎这件事
It's for Sophie, it means a lot to her,
而且她有把枪
and she has a gun.
庆祝派对是傻逼娘们的玩意
Well, showers are stupid girl things
这位汉子不想沾上边
that this guy wants no part of.
姑娘们
Hey, girls!
看  我在给你们的小蛋糕生意打广告
Look. I'm advertising your cupcake business.
你的确是在广告某物  不过不是我们的小蛋糕
You're advertising something, but it's not our cupcakes.
我送了我们楼里的人免费T恤
I gave out free T-shirts to our building.
我在每一户的门前放了一件
I left one by everyone's door.
苏菲家放了两件  桑切斯家16件
Two at Sophie's, 16 at the Sanchez's.
所以他家还有6个孩子得分享T恤
So about six of the kids will have to share.
有意思  所以我们的衣服在罗德尼
Interesting. Now our shirts are available at both Rodney,
一家曼哈顿高级精品服饰店
the high-end Manhattan boutique,
以及一栋永远闻起来带点汽油味的
and an apartment building that always smells
公寓大楼里皆可取得
a little like gasoline.
请不要再谈我不是主角的事情了
Well, please stop talking about things that aren't me.
姑娘们
Now girls,
你们准备好我明天婚前派对的蛋糕了吗
did you get the cake for my wedding shower tomorrow?
什么  我还得做个蛋糕是吗
Oh, was I supposed to make a cake?
我还真啥也没为这个派对准备啊
I've literally done nothing for this shower.
甚至连个澡也懒得洗
I haven't even taken a bath.
不要  我的蛋糕不要是这里做的
Oh, no, I'm not getting my cake from here.
这可是我的婚前派对
No, this is my bridal shower.
我想要从巴斯罗缤冰激凌与
Yeah, I want to get something classic from Baskin Robbins
唐恩都乐甜甜圈店合一的店买蛋糕
that's also a Dunkin' Donuts.
现在两家合一了吗
They mix those two now?
简直就是抽大麻的人美梦成真啊
It's a stoner's dream come true.
我尽量布置我们的公寓了
I tried to make our apartment look nice.
我甚至还搬动了张椅子去档污渍
I even moved a chair to cover a stain,
结果那张椅子原来位子底下更让人无法直视
but what was under the chair was so much worse.
我想我要说的是  请别射爆我们
I guess what I'm saying is, please don't shoot us.
我也没期望你家能变多漂亮
Well, I don't expect it to look that good.
给猪戴个大礼帽也是白搭
I mean, you can't put a silk hat on a pig.
我真有亲自试验过哦
And I know, 'cause I tried once.
麦克斯  我的天啊  你干了什么好事
Max! Oh, my God! What have you done?
我发现我不想吃我不爱吃的东西
I realized I don't like a strawberry center.
而我也不想因此就吃不下睡不着
And I am not going to beat myself up about it.
我叫你去买皱纸彩带来
When I told you to get crepe paper streamers
布置婚前派对  是让你买粉色  不是黑色
and decorate for the shower, I meant with pink, not black.
我们是帮苏菲办婚前派对
It's a wedding shower for Sophie,
不是给婴儿鬼片办派对
not a baby shower for Rosemary's Baby.
干嘛啊  我说了不懂娘们的玩意
What? I told you, I don't do girl things.
我不懂挂粉红  或者坐着尿尿
Like hang pink or sit when I pee.
巧合的是  我称呼站着尿尿为"挂粉红"
Which, coincidentally, I refer to as "Hanging pink."
天啊  那是什么味道
My God, what is that smell?
这里绝对有东西坏掉了
Something's really gone bad here.
除了我们人生之外的东西
Besides our lives.
是哪个波兰食物
It's the Polish food.
我觉得其中有个香肠是用旧人字拖做的
I think one of those sausages is made of old flip-flops.
有人已经到了吗
Someone's here already?
波兰人都会提早到的吗
Are Polish people always early?
我是不是对他们无知了
Is that a stereotype I don't know about?
天啊
Oh my God!
为我办的婚前派对吗
A wedding shower for me?
如果我事先知道  我就会好好打扮一番了
I mean, if I had known, I would have dressed!
苏菲  你明明就知道
Sophie, you did know.
是啊  我就提早下来练习几套进场方式
I know. I came down early to practice some entrances.
准备好看进场方式二吧
Now get ready for entrance number two.
你有为让人进"二号后庭场"准备过吗
Are you ever ready for entrance number two?
谁啊
Who is it?
天啊
Oh my God!
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
今天是我的婚前派对
Oh, it's the day of my wedding shower.
没有比这更美好的事情了
Could anything be more wonderful?
我又感动  又惊喜
I was moved, I was surprised.
比读原著还精彩
I liked it better than the book.
先过来帮忙辨识这些波兰食物吧
Now, come on in here and identify some of this Polish food
这样我好知道今晚我不该吃什么
so I can know what I'm not eating tonight.
我不要在我婚前派对上吃东西
Oh, no. I'm not eating at my shower.
我要假装我有饮食失调症
I'm pretending I have an eating disorder
这样大家才会觉得我十全十美
so everyone will think that I have it all.
我觉得你会很高兴的
I think you're going to be happy.
因为我准备了很多好玩的派对游戏
I have lots of fun shower games,
首先是"谁最了解苏菲"
starting with "Who Knows The Most About Sophie?"
这游戏我肯定会赢
Oh, I'll win that one. Yeah.
苏菲得去撒尿了
And Sophie's got to tinkle.
看到没  这么了解肯定稳赢
See? I'm a shoo-in.
哇  我的天啊
Oh. Oh, my gosh.
黑色的厕纸
Black toilet paper.
姑娘们  这细节好
Oh, nice touch, girls.
我喜欢不知道何时才完事的神秘感
Yeah, I love the mystery of not knowing when you're done.
联调局  开门
FBI! Open up!
联调局  他们没回复要来吧
The FBI? I don't think they RSVP'd.
估计是来抓我的
Oh, that's got to be for me.
不是我干的
I didn't do it.
顺便告诉你
And just so you know,
我在纽瓦克市干的那件事  法律追溯期过了
the statute of limitations is up on that Newark thing.
小姐  我不是来逮捕你的
I'm not here to arrest you, miss.
这下好了  是抓我
Great, it's me.
麦克斯  我就告诉你非法下载电影是有罪的
Max, I told you pirating movies was a real crime.
现在我要为《五十度灰》去坐牢了
Now I'm going to jail for Fifty Shades Of Grey.
的确有人该为这部戏去坐牢
Someone should.
我懂你  男主角跟我想象中差太多
I hear you, not the Christian Grey I'd pictured.
我是联调局的德雷克探员
I'm Agent Drake with the FBI.
不用不安  但你们楼里有名男子
Nothing to get upset about, but there's a man in your building
在他的公寓里  挟持三名女子长达数月之久
who's been holding three women hostage in his apartment for months.
听起来很有可能
Yeah, that sounds about right.
其中一名被挟持女子成功逃脱
Now, one of the captives escaped today
并通知了有关当局
and alerted authorities.
估计是走廊上跟我擦肩而过尖叫跑掉的女人
Oh, that must have been the lady I passed screaming in the hall.
干嘛  咱们这栋楼里
What? There is a fine line between "hostage"
"人质"与"没吃药"只有一线之隔
and "off your meds" in this building.
所以飞虎队要拯救楼上另外两个人质
So, a SWAT team is going in for the other two still upstairs.
但我们得先疏散楼里住户
But we need to evacuate the building first.
走吧
So let's go.
好吧  首先我可以先跟你谈清楚几件事吗
All right, can I just put a few things away first.
因为如果有警察会进来的话
You know, because I want the place to look nice
我希望先"打扫干净"
if there's going to be police in here.
小姐  我才不在乎
Look, miss, whatever drugs you're hiding in here,
你这里藏了什么毒品
I couldn't care less.
我们现在得立刻疏散
We need to get out now.
你知道你就是我的理想型吗
You know, you're just my type of guy.
你不在乎我吸毒嗑药  而且在我面前不用等
You don't mind my drug use and you're already here.
爽呀
Oh, yeah!
你们给我叫了一个警察装脱衣舞男吗
You girls ordered a cop stripper for my bridal shower?
新娘现在要来享用啦
Oh, here comes the bride all right!
来吧  来吧
Come on. Yeah.
你们看  他喜欢我
Yeah, see? Look, he likes me.
我不敢相信我居然跟一个
I cannot believe I live in this building
会对女性做出如此恶劣行为的人住一栋楼
with a man who would do something so awful.
我也不敢相信我住在这栋大楼里
Also, cannot believe I live in this building.
你知道我觉得是谁吗
You know who I think it is?
有猫味没猫男
Smells Like Cats But Has No Cats.
是吗  感觉他不像这么有实践力的人啊
Really? He doesn't seem like a go-getter.
我觉得是三奶头无鼻男
I think it's Three Nipples No Nose.
三奶头无鼻男吗  人家可好了好吧
Three Nipples No Nose? He's a delight.
苏菲  这很扫兴吧
Sophie, isn't this upsetting?
当然啊
It sure is.
警察脱衣舞男怎么样都不让我拖他裤子
I couldn't get that stripper cop to take his pants off.
看  那里有几个我请来的宾客呢
Hey, look, there's some of my shower guests.
苏菲  你好啊
Sophie, hi.
你看
Oh, look.
看到没  那就是我朋友娜塔莉亚
And see? That one's my friend Natalya.
我以前跟你说过的
The one I told you about.
是啊  身上好多多出来的皮肤
Yeah, there's all that extra skin.
你之前还真没夸张
Ew. You were not exaggerating.
她一生下来就这样了
She was born with all that skin.
她高中的时候
She had a chip clip on her back
脖子后面得用夹子夹起皮肤
all through high school.
我知道楼上那家伙很扫兴
Yeah, I know that guy upstairs is a real bummer,
但你知道什么能让我开心点吗
but you know what would help?
比如让我拆礼物
If I could open my presents.
是啊
Yeah.
惨了
Oh, no!
抱歉  你们不能过去
Sorry, you can't go through,
那条子不让我朋友进来
The fuzz isn't letting them through!
干嘛这样
Oh, come on.
太不公平了  几分钟前你们才让一男的进去
No fair, they just let a guy in here a few minutes ago.
就因为你的朋友们不是寻炸弹狗
Just 'cause your friends aren't bomb-sniffing dogs,
就不能进来吗  烂
they can't get in? Boo!
姑娘们  把你们的礼物传给警察
Hey, look, ladies, pass your presents up to the cops.
警察  把我的礼物传给我
Cops, pass my presents to me.
等等  苏菲  在你开礼物之前
Wait, Sophie, before you open them,
我真的得记录下来谁送了你什么
I really want to write down who got you what.
然后留下那漂亮的缎带  给你做缎带帽
And save that pretty ribbon, I'm gonna make you a bow hat!
瞧你
Look at you.
上帝派了一疯子来挟持姑娘
Making lemonade out of a maniac
而你却把握机会转亏为盈
holding three innocent women hostage.
购物券
Oh, a gift card.
送回去
Oh, send it back.
苏菲  我们乐意替你收下
Sophie, we would've taken that.
虽然不知道是哪家的
I don't know what is was for,
但我知道我们一定很乐意收下
I just know that we would've taken it.
不要  我要送回去
No, I'm sending it back.
我想要的是礼物  不是多一件差事
I want a gift, not another errand.
虽然从包装看来我不是很喜欢
Oh, yeah, not in love with the paper, but...
但我会等到拆开后再决定
well, I'll wait till I open it to judge.
两位  这边
Hi. Excuse me.
打扰了
Excuse me?
我是玛利亚·阿隆索-冈萨雷斯
I'm Maria Alonso-Gonzalez.
两位女士可以跟第2频道
Could you ladies talk to Channel 2
说说今晚的骇人发现吗
about tonight's disturbing discovery?
-不可以  -可以啊
- No. - Yes.
听我和我商业头脑的就好
Just go with me and my business savvy.
当然可以  玛利亚·阿隆索-冈萨雷斯
Yes, Maria Alonso-Gonzalez,
我们可以回答几个问题
we can answer a few questions.
请问有任何迹象表明你们楼里
Were there any signs at all that something of this nature
可能会发生这种事情吗
was going on in your building?
希望警察能将我们楼里的变态绳之于法
We just hope they bring this sick freak in our building to justice
这样我们才能安心回到
so that we can return to work
麦克斯自制小蛋糕店工作
at Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
摄像机对准大门  他来了
Get on the door. Here he comes.
谁啊  这个变态到底是谁
Who is it? Who is this sick freak?
不是我干的
It's not me.
是我吗
Is it?
我也不确定  罪名是什么来着
I'm not sure, what are the charges?
另一变态
Different sick freak.
鲁拉  乌玛  格里塔  快看
Hey, Rula, Uma, Greta, look.
就是他
This is him.
这位就是准新郎
This is the groom-to-be.
别管楼上那个家伙了
Forget about the guy upstairs,
这家伙才是卧室里真正的疯子
this is the real maniac in the bedroom.
居然是他
That's him?
啤酒肚运动短裤男
Beer Belly Gym Shorts?
真是想不到啊
Never would've guessed.
糟糕  他穿着我们的T恤呢
Oh, no. He's wearing one of our shirts.
苍天啊
Why?
大地啊
他一个胖子为什么要穿中号啊
Why is he wearing a medium?
安啦  没人会注意到是我们的
I mean, nobody's gonna see that.
警察已经将嫌犯逮捕
Police have just apprehended the suspect
而现在大家最关心的问题是
and the question on everyone's mind is,
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
"What does Max's Homemade Cupcakes
跟整个事件到底有何联系"
have to do with this?"
我们无可奉告
We have no comment.
无未来  无除臭剂
Or future, or deodorant.
所以别来烦我们了
So leave us alone!
媒体是怎么发现我们就在
How did they find out we work in this dump,
破楼隔壁的破餐厅上班
next door to the other dump?
我的话让我意识到我们的事业
As I'm saying it, I realize our career
是由两个破地方[粪堆]组成的
is made up of two dumps.
听起来我们的事业喝太多咖啡了[利便]
Sounds like our career has been drinking too much coffee.
报纸上全都在报道这件事
The story is all over the paper.
他们称被困的女人为"小蛋糕人质"
They're calling those ladies "The Cupcake Captives,"
那个男的为"小蛋糕绑匪"
calling that guy "The Cupcake Captor,"
这整件事为"小蛋糕惨案"
and calling the whole thing "The Cupcake Catastrophe."
不过你们无须担心这事会严重影响
But you needn't worry about it reflecting badly
你们的小蛋糕生意
on your cupcake business.
天啊  就连时尚版都写了这事
Oh, no. It's even in the fashion section.
上面有一张我们T恤的图片  写着
There's a picture of our shirts and it says,
"死都不该穿什么"
"What not to wear, ever."
好啦  各位冷静
Okay. Everybody calm down.
这句话主要是讲给我自己听
I'm mostly talking to myself.
媒体就这样
The media is just going to do its thing.
我以前也被头条中伤过
I've been slandered in the headlines before.
我被称为"庞氏公主"  "破产芭比"
I was called "Ponzi Princess," "Bankrupt Barbie."
现在回想起来  那真是最美好的时代啊
Looking back, those were the best of times.
你们好啊  我正准备拿这一盘
Oh, hello. I was just about to take a tray
麦克斯和卡洛琳酒去给我的记者朋友喝呢
of Max and Carolines out to my reporter friends.
抱歉  你可以把这几杯麦克斯和卡洛琳酒
Sorry, you can give those Max and Carolines
给你面前的麦克斯和卡洛琳喝
to this Max and Caroline.
各位好啊
Hi, everybody.
我好低落哦
Oh, I'm depressed.
很明显  因为今日我戴的假发量"低"于平时
See, you can tell 'cause I'm only wearing half my hair.
姑娘们  我看见这箱子放在你家门口
Girls, I found this box outside your door.
我还以为是派对礼物呢
And I was hoping it was a shower present.
因为我的大日子被那几个自私的女人质毁了
Since those selfish hostage girls ruined my special day.
真晦气  老娘连一顶操蛋的缎带帽都没捞着
Oh, man. I didn't even get a freakin' ribbon hat.
你想要我用黄色警示线做的抹胸吗
Do you want the tube top I made out of the police tape?
我称其为"警示胸"
I'm calling it a tape top.
专利申请中
Patent pending.
各位  别这样
Come on, you guys.
这事重点不在我们
This isn't about us.
我们得摆正心态看待它
We need to put this all in perspective.
我们安全健康地活着  而且...
We're all safe, and healthy, and--
我勒个去  正当我觉得再也无法忍受时
Oh, my God, just when I can't take anymore,
"再也"来了
here comes anymore.
"现将本店你们T恤的剩余存货归还
"We are returning the remainder of your t-shirt stock.
该产品与一起正在调查的刑事案件的主嫌犯有关
Our Rodney brand cannot be associated with a product
罗德尼品牌不能与之有任何联系
at the center of an ongoing criminal investigation.
双方合同作废"
Consider our contract null and void."
真是太令人震惊了
This is so shocking.
麦克斯  你居然识字
Max, you can read?
所以你只是不想跟顾客介绍特价菜而已
So you just didn't want to tell people the specials.
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
我们等了这么久  就等着小蛋糕T恤出名
We waited so long for something to happen to our cupcake t-shirts.
为什么是那家伙
Why that guy?
偏偏就那一天他决定不穿
And on the one day he chooses to not wear
他那件放屁T恤
his "Pull my finger" shirt.
我是玛利亚·阿隆索-冈萨雷斯
This is Maria Alonso-Gonzalez,
-正在现场为您报道  -麦克斯  你在干什么
- reporting to you live... - Max, what are you doing?
-这里是麦克斯自制小蛋糕店  -他们会发现我们的
- from Max's Homemade Cupcakes. -  They'll see us.
不会的
No they won't,
因为所有摄像机正对准阿憨呢
Because all the cameras are on Han right now.
你能简单地跟我们介绍一下
Can you talk a little bit about the women
麦克斯自制小蛋糕店的两位店主吗
behind Max's Homemade Cupcakes?
这么说吧  麦克斯和卡洛琳
Well, let's just say Max and Caroline
她俩对工作过敏  情况大致跟
are allergic to work, much in the same way
呆伯特对周一过敏一样  都不想工作
Dilbert is allergic to Mondays.
换个话题  玛利亚·阿隆索-冈萨雷斯
Moving on, Maria Alonso-Gonzalez,
你要不要去威廉斯堡餐厅
would you care to come into The Williamsburg Diner,
贝德福德大道6355号
6355 Bedford Avenue,
营业时间是早上八点到凌晨两点
open 8:00 A.M. till 2:00 A.M.,
喝一杯特色酒  "小蛋糕人质"大都会鸡尾酒
for our signature drink: The Cupcake Captive Cosmo?
而男士们可以来一杯  "人质"鳕鱼角鸡尾酒
And for you gents, The Captive Cape Cod?
把那些小蛋糕从垃圾袋里拿出来
Hey, get these cupcakes out of the garbage.
留点地方给我装阿憨的尸体
I need to make room for Han's body.
我要把头留着用来警示其他背叛我们的人
I'm keeping the head as a warning to others who cross us.
我们要跟媒体安排一次采访
We need to take back our t-shirts' image
好让他们拿掉我们T恤的照片
by setting up an interview with the news.
我说的"我们"是指你一个人
And by "We," I mean you.
听着  我看《美国警察》学会了一件事
Look, if I learned one thing from my time on Cops,
那就是我可以在3秒内跳过栅栏
it's that I can hop a fence in three seconds flat.
我学会的第二件事是
If I learned two things,
镜头之前  没罪让我看起来也有罪
it's that the camera makes me look guilty.
尤其是香蕉共和国服装店的监控镜头
Especially when it's a security camera at Banana Republic.
反正我不行
I can't do it.
我不能让全世界知道卡洛琳·钱宁
The world can't know that Caroline Channing
牵扯进另一件备受关注的罪案
is involved in another high-profile crime.
而且连指甲都不保养一下
And hasn't kept up her nail maintenance, like, at all.
好吧
Fine.
如果我从《美国警察》学会的第三件事是
Because if I learned three things from Cops,
最好趁早投降  而且别不穿衣服
it's that it's best to surrender early and not naked.
真的很感谢你能抽空接受我们的采访
We really appreciate you taking the time to talk to us.
如果你真的想谢我
If you really want to thank me,
不如在拷问我时  给我的脸打上马赛克
how about I get some pixels up over my grill?
有些孩子在找我  你们会在无形中帮了他们
I got some kids looking for me and they don't need the help.
我们做不了
We don't have the capability to do that.
这是直播电视
This is live TV.
可以弄个那种能扭曲声音的装置吗
How about one of those voice distorting machines?
就是让我的声音听起来像一个胖变形金刚
You know, make my voice sound like a fat Transformer.
也不行
Um, no.
没关系
No problem.
那就我自己来吧
I'll take care of that myself.
以前也碰到过这种状况
Been in this sitch before.
好了  倒数三  二
All right, in 3, 2...
晚上好  这里是威廉斯堡
Good evening. In Williamsburg...
麦克斯  我就在旁边  以防你需要我
Max, I'm right here, if you need me.
我能行
I got this.
令人震惊的"小蛋糕人质"事件
Now infamous in the shocking "Cupcake Captives" story.
我身旁的是店主  麦克斯·布莱克
I'm here with the owner, Max Black.
你好  玛利亚
Hi, Maria.
麦克斯  当你看到理查德·格里芬
Max, how upset were you to see that Richard Griffin
是你们店的超级粉丝时  你有多难过
was Max's Homemade Cupcakes' biggest fan?
我当时很难过
I was really upset.
够了  大家好  我插句话
Okay, hi. Stepping in.
麦克斯显然被这一切搞得非常难过
Max is clearly so upset by all this
以至于她失去了理智
that she's lost her mind.
尽管这次我真的很需要她
The one time I really needed her, anyway.
你好  玛利亚
Hi, Maria.
在把衣服卖给一个强行将三名女子
How will your company's reputation recover
囚禁在公寓里的男人后
from doing business with a man
你们公司的声誉如何能从这次危机中恢复
who held three women in his apartment against their will?
人们会做可怕的事情
Look, people do terrible things.
而且在做的时候  他们会穿着衣服
And they do them wearing shirts.
那不代表衣服就是邪恶的啊
That doesn't make the shirt evil.
如果是一件衣服犯下罪行  那把它关起来好啦
Now, if a shirt commits a crime, lock it up.
我肯定双手赞成
You'll get no argument from me.
用我回来接受访问吗
Should I jump back in?
我能行
I got this.
好了  访问时间到
Okay, yeah. That's all the time we have.
谢谢两位
Thank you.
也谢谢你
卡洛琳  谢谢你试图为我举办派对
Caroline, thank you for trying to throw me a shower.
我们从来不是真正的朋友  关系也不亲密
I mean, we were never really friends or close.
没错  我一看见跟我要同时拿信
And yeah, I run away when I see you heading towards
我都会立马撒腿跑了
the mailboxes the same time as me--
别一个劲儿地谢我了
Please stop thanking me.
想来我们家吗
Hey. Want to come to our place?
那些猪脚应该还没坏
Those pig feet haven't gone bad.
大概吧  反正也吃不出来
I guess. It's hard to tell.
好啊  拇指甲下面的肉最好吃了
Yeah. The best meat's under the toe nails.
是吗
Is it?
惊喜吧
Surprise.
老天  这是怎么回事
Oh, my God, what's all this?
天啊  我好惊喜啊
Oh, no. I'm so surprised.
不  这次是真的被惊喜到了
No, I really am this time.
-我也是  -我也是
- So am I. - Me, too.
吃了这根香肠  我才知道我吃过
Until this sausage, I thought the grossest thing
最恶心的食物不是甘蓝菜
I'd ever eaten was kale.
我的老天  真不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe it.
没有比这更美好的事情了
Could anything be more wonderful?
麦克斯 真不敢相信这都是你布置的
Max, I can't believe you did all this.
我以为你回家是做你平时
I thought you came home to do what you usually do
低落时做的事情
when you get depressed.
喝个烂醉  朝门廊的人竖中指
Get drunk and throw the finger at people from the stoop.
没有门廊那部分  但我的确是醉了
No stoop. But I am drunk.
你觉得我清醒的时候能做这种事吗
You think I could've done this sober?
我想到最近一切都太黑太晦气了
I just figured, with everything around us being so black lately,
所以我们需要来点粉红色
I thought we needed a little pink.
你说得对  我们的确需要
You're right. We did.
因为我们的T恤生意已经完了
'Cause our t-shirt business is over.
可我们还是得还银行那笔贷款  现在该怎么办
And we still have to pay off that bank loan. Now what?
我们会想到办法的  一如既往逢凶化吉
We'll figure something out. We always do.
姑娘们  快过来
Hey, girls, come quick.
我们要玩"猜猜苏菲最爱的性交体位"
We're gonna play "Guess Sophie's Favorite Sex Position"
背入式  还要一边看《逍遥法外》哦
It's on all fours, watching How To Get Away With Murder.
瞧  我就说我会赢嘛
See? I told you I was gonna win.
一瞬间又黑了
And it just got black again.
是啊  整个人生都黑了
Yeah, real black.
这块糖是湿的
This is wet!
麦克斯  你是不是之前吃过了
Max, did you already eat this?
我跟你说过啊  我不喜欢草莓夹心糖
I told you, I don't like a strawberry center.
我也不想吃我不爱吃的东西
And I am not gonna beat myself up about it.